onepunchmango.net 2017-01-10

# Privacy Policy - GoGoAnime

This privacy policy is intended to inform you about the types of information gathered by GoGoAnime.ch when you visit GoGoAnime.ch.

Log Files  
We may automatically and through third-party tracking services (e.g., Google Analytics) gather certain non-personally identifiable information about your use of GoGoAnime.ch and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps, and related data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, solely to improve the quality of our services. Out of respect for your privacy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

COOKIES  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and tracking cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use GoGoAnime.ch. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We use tracking cookies to better understand how you use GoGoAnime.ch, and to enhance your user experience. A tracking cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while using GoGoAnime.ch.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
We may periodically update this policy. If you are a GoGoAnime.ch member, we will attempt to notify you of material updates by sending a notice to an email address you may have provided to us. Otherwise, you may view the updated version of this policy on the GoGoAnime.ch website.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
